<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yin Minn Pa Pa</title>
    <link>https://www.yinminnpapa.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yin Minn Pa Pa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 10:43:29 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.yinminnpapa.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.yinminnpapa.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 10:43:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinminnpapa.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>Yin Minn Pa Pa, Katsunari Yoshioka, Tsutomu Matsumoto “ Search Engine Based Investigation on Misconfiguration of Zone Transfer”, International Workshop on Security (IWSEC-2012), Fukuoka, Japan, 2012 November, {POSTER}. pdf
 Yin Minn Pa Pa, Katsunari Yoshioka, Tsutomu Matsumoto &amp;ldquo;Search Engine Based Investigation on Misconfiguration of Zone Transfer”, Asia Joint Conference on Information Security (Asia-JCIS), Seoul, Korea, 2013 July.{Best Paper Award} pdf
 Yin Minn Pa Pa, Daisuke Makita, Katsunari Yoshioka, Tsutomu Matsumoto “Finding Malicious Authoritative DNS server”, Information and Communication System Security (ICSS), Yokohama, Japan, 2013 March.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First</title>
      <link>https://www.yinminnpapa.com/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 00:35:11 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinminnpapa.com/post/first/</guid>
      <description>မြန်စံ မြန်မာ၃စတန်း
မြန်မာ၃ရိုးရိုး
မြန်မာ၃ရိုးရိုး
မြန်မာလိုမြင်ရပါသလား</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello my Dear Reader!</title>
      <link>https://www.yinminnpapa.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.yinminnpapa.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Yin Minn Pa Pa, originally from Myanmar and currently working at Japan as security researcher. I finished Dr.Eng. (Doctor of Engineering) in Information Science from Yokohama National University, Japan.This site is made to document my professional life and to help burmese students interested in information security.
You can find list of my research publications here.
Following is brief about me.
Research interests:
1. Network security 2. Malware Analysis 3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>